coverpageapp.com 2016-10-15

# CoverPage - Privacy Policy

_This document was last updated: 12. February 2015 by CoverPage Team_

**CoverPage s.r.o. (CoverPage)** wants you to be informed and comfortable about all our actions that help us provide our services and deliver you best and secure user experience.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or country, field of interest. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We also collect downloaded digital publications.  
For that purpose we use tools like Google Analytics or Apple iTunes to more understand what our customers like and if there is any room for improvements of quality. 

## What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * **To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * **To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies? 

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade to third parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential, including without limitation, the device's ID like (iOS UDID). We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing and advertising.

## Google Analytics features

We have implemented these features based on Display Advertising:

  * Remarketing
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting

We are using Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. CoverPage and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to this website.  
CoverPage and third-party vendors, including Google, also use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to this site.  
Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with all acts governing data and privacy protection. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of online privacy protection of children, we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Data Storage

CoverPage uses third party hosting partners to provide the hardware, networking, storage and related technology required to run our services.

## Use of the CoverPage Service

The CoverPage Service is accessible through the Site and installed Authoring software tool. This service enables customers to create digital publications, upload videos and pictures and publish digital content into customer's account or to decide whether it will be published to the public space viewable within CoverPage iPad Reader application. This iPad Reader application is available for free to anybody without needed registration on our site. Please note that any information you disclose through this content uploaded via the CoverPage Service may become public information and may be available to users within iPad Reader application where they are posted and to the general public. **We are not responsible for the content that you publish through the CoverPage Service.** For more information about terms and conditions about nature of your content, please visit our Terms and Conditions section at <http://www.coverpageapp.com/en/terms>

## Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.coverpageapp.com/en/terms>

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without prior notice.

## Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.coverpageapp.com  
Ilkovicova 6276  
Bratislava 842 16  
Slovakia, EU  
info@coverpageapp.com
